《地球百子》前情提要
Previously on "The 100"...
原創翻譯  雙語字幕
■
僅供學習 禁止用於任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.ZiMuZu.tv
這件事根本不在乎你來自哪一個家族
This thing doesn't care what clan you're from.
翻譯：zeez  喵球球
■
它控制人一個人在一個時間
It controls people one person at a time
直到有沒有人離開
until there is no one left.
翻譯：zeez  喵球球  阿飄
阻止她的唯一辦法是把信息
The only way to stop her is to get the information
從火種中獲取  而唯一的辦法就是把它
off the flame, and the only way to do that
校對:阿飄
放在美國安大略的頭部
is to put it in ontari's head.
這是一個殺人開關
It's a kill switch.
如果我能得到這個工作 我可以殺死異形
If I can get this to work,i can kill alie.
時間軸：風吹來的那片雲
賈斯珀已經碎裂
Jasper's been chipped.
你所要做的就是破壞機器
All you have to do is destroy the machine,
她會很好 保證
and she'll be fine,promise.
後期：吉吉  總監：阿飄
林肯死了
Lincoln is dead.
他是我的家
He was my home.
打開微信   掃瞄左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    美劇炸了
瞭解最新影視資訊字幕信息
我們在找到一臺主機前
Until we find it a host,
沒有辦法阻止阿莉
we won't know how to stop alie.
那我們就找一臺主機
Then let's find it a host.
我們不能讓他們得到你
We can't let them have you.
不
No!
啊
Uh!
她已經腦死亡了 結束了
She's brain dead. It's over.
我們被困在這裡了
We're trapped here.
啊 啊
Aah! Aah!
Agh! Uhh!
啊 啊
Uh...Uh...
媽媽
Mom?
能聽見我說話嗎
Can you hear me?
我知道真正的你還在
I know you're in there.
快醒醒
Come back to me.
我需要你
I need you.
-克拉克  -我在呢
- Clarke. - Yeah.
你沒事  你沒事了  來
You're ok. You're ok. Here.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
-對不起  -沒事
- I'm sorry. -It's ok.
我對不起你
I'm so sorry.
沒事的
It's ok.
別哭了
Hey, stop.
-我錯了  -那不是真的你
- I'm sorry. - It wasn't you.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
不是你幹的
No. It wasn't you.
-媽媽  -不
- Mom... - No.
我需要你幫忙
I need your help.
別開槍  她沒事
Hey, no. It's ok.
我給她用了電磁脈衝  她回來了
I used the emp. She's back.
那安塔麗怎麼辦
W-w-well, what about Ontari?
你不是說那個只能用一次嗎
Thought you said we had one shot with that thing.
我說了
I told you,
安塔麗已經不能接受火種了
Ontari's no longer an option for the flame.
她已經腦死亡了
She's brain dead.
這層樓安全嗎
Is the floor secure?
暫時安全  亞哈和守衛被綁在臥室裡
For now. Jaha and the guards are tied up in a bedroom.
我們上來的途中
We took out the elevator
炸掉了電梯和樓梯
and the ladder as we climbed.
樓梯都塌了  沒人跟上來
The stairs are collapsed. No one's following us.
那我們就有時間了
Good. Then we have time.
但沒有下去的路
What we don't have is a way down.
用來幹什麼的時間
Time for what?
完成登基儀式
An ascension ceremony.
登基  你剛說安塔麗已經不能登基了
Ascension? You just said Ontari wasn't an option.
而且她還帶著芯片  沒有電磁脈衝可用了
Besides, she's still chipped, and we no longer have an emp.
芯片不放進安塔麗腦中
We're not putting the flame in Ontari's head.
而是放進我的腦中
We're putting it in mine.
克拉克  那玩意幾秒鐘內就殺了埃莫森
Clarke, that thing killed emerson in seconds,
溶解了他的大腦
liquefied his brain.
埃莫森沒有和夜之血脈聯結
Emerson wasn't connected to a nightblood.
-輸液嗎  -不完全是
- Transfusion? - Not exactly.
像韋瑟山那樣的聯結
Connected like Mount Weather.
是的  我們需要的都在你的醫療包裡
Yes. Everything we need is in your med kit.
不  這太危險了
No. It's too dangerous,
有太多變數
and there are too many variables.
但我們別無選擇
But no options.
好了
OK.
不管你在幹什麼  要抓緊時間了
Whatever you're doing, you better do it fast.
怎麼了  出什麼事了
Why? What happened?
他們在往上爬
They're climbing.
我必須這麼做
I have to do this.
好吧  那我幫你
Ok. I'll help you.
《地球百子》
第三季  第十六集
[本季終]
你們沒時間了
Guys, you're running out of time.
要雷文的機器  還是要哈珀
What's it gonna be, Raven's machine or Harper?
別給他
Don't give it to them.
一直和他說話
Just keep him talking.
住手  你沒有理由傷害她
Stop. There's no reason to hurt her.
你可以阻止的  只要你開門
You can stop it. Just open the door.
那我們開了門以後呢
And if we do that, then what,
反正還是要吞芯片
we get chipped, anyway?
雷文  你找到自殺指令的幾率
Raven, your chances of reaching
不到百分之二
the kill switch again are less than 2%.
我加了特別防衛
I've added additional security.
我知道漢娜給蒙蒂的芯片的
I know the digital signature of the chip
電子序列號
that Hannah gave to Monty.
你使用該門戶通過我的代碼內的
The moment you use the portal to interact
任何關卡  我都會知道
with anything within my code, I will know.
我會找到你的
I will find you.
你真的要為了百分之二的幾率害死朋友嗎
Are you really willing to let your friend die for a 2% chance?
你覺得呢
What do you think?
-你還好嗎  -沒事
- You ok? - Yeah.
還好光之城裡沒有痛苦
Good thing there's no pain in the City of Light.
陽臺上澆了油
Balcony's greased.
沒人能從這邊進來
No one's getting in through here.
幹得好
Good.
燈油只夠塗滿除司令臥室以外的
There's enough lamp oil to cover every window on the floor
每扇窗戶
except the commander's chambers.
那麼那裡就是戰鬥開始的地方了
Then that's where the fighting starts.
我們去那守著
We'll dig in there.
小奧
O.
小心
Be careful.
我們都準備好了
We're all set.
好了  你準備好了嗎
Ok. You ready?
是的
Yeah.
試著倒立一下
Hey, try doing that hanging upside down.
會起作用的
This will work.
如果沒用呢
And if it doesn't?
如果沒用  她就會死
If it doesn't work, then she dies.
如果她不試  那等他們爬上來
If she doesn't try, then she dies with the rest of us
她們和我們一起死
when the climbers get here.
如果我們要做的話  把火種給我
If we're gonna do this, I need the flame.
媽媽  拜託  他知道自己在做什麼
Mom, please. He knows what he's doing.
你就任我去做吧
You have to let me go.
前傾
Lean forward.
-準備好了嗎  -好了  來吧
- You ready? - Yeah. Do it.
勇往直前
Ascende superius.
不不不
No, no, no.
-她還好嗎  -她的心跳加快了
- She ok? - Her heart's racing.
把拿東西從她腦袋裡拿出來
Get that thing out of her head.
我說  把那玩意從她腦袋裡拿出來
I said, get that thing out of her head!
不  不
No. No...
還不行
Not yet.
你疼嗎
Are you in any pain?
不  我沒事
No. I'm ok.
我知道要怎麼阻止阿莉了
I know how to stop ALIE.
我得吞下芯片
I have to take the chip.
什麼
What?
我得去光之城
I have to go into the City of Light
找到自殺指令
and find the kill switch.
好  真是個好主意
Yeah. That sounds like a great idea.
克拉克  聽我說  阿莉想要火種
Clarke, listen to me. ALIE wants the flame.
如果你吞下芯片  就等於拱手呈上
If you take the chip, you're giving it to her.
一有人看到你
The second someone see you,
阿莉就會知道你去了那裡
ALIE is gonna know that you're there.
她會殺掉你
She'll kill you.
如果你的意識死了  那你就真的死了
If your mind dies, you die.
火種會保護我
The flame will protect me.
我不知道我是從何而知的  我就是知道
I don't know how I know. I just...know.
我相信你
I believe you.
你知道自己要找什麼嗎
Do you even know what you're looking for?
我找到時就知道了
I'll know when I find it.
願我們重逢
May we meet again.
我們會的
We will.
我們會確保你的安全
We'll keep you safe.
賈斯珀
Jasper?
怎...
What--
他們看不到我
They can't see me.
克拉克
Clarke...
-你燒得很厲害  -我沒事
- You're burning up. - I'm fine.
傷口感染了
Wound is infected.
很抱歉出了這樣的事
I'm sorry about the way things happened.
那是另一場戰爭
That was another war.
最好帶他去艾比那裡
Better take him to Abby.
收到  我馬上回來
Copy that. I'll come right back.
我不會讓你獨自抵抗的
I'm not letting you fight alone.
他不是獨自一人
He won't be alone.
看到了吧  走
You see? Come on.
如果我們想活下去
If we're gonna survive this,
就得並肩作戰
we'll need to stand together.
現在你說了這樣的話
Now you say that.
該死  太快了
Damn, that was fast.
他們來了
Here they come.
好  第一波人不多
Ok. The first wave is small.
我們照你哥哥的辦法做
We do this your brother's way.
我們讓他們進來  打倒他們
We let them in. We take them down.
然後把他們綁起來  明白了嗎
We tie them up. Clear?
你把她和派克留在那裡
You left her with Pike?
小奧  你在做什麼
O., what are you doing?
貝拉米  不
Bellamy, no.
來  你還能站起來嗎
Come on. Can you stand?
她給了我一刀
She cut me.
來  我們得走了
Come on. We got to go.
-我們不能放棄這個房間  -我們已經放棄了
- But we can't give up the room. - We already have.
幫我
Help me.
我說過了  你得控制好自己
I told you, you need to get yourself
如果想活下去  就克制好
Under control if we're gonna survive this.
聽我說
Listen to me.
我明白你的感受
I know how you feel.
我任由自己想復仇的渴望
I let my need for revenge
讓自己站錯了邊
put me on the wrong side.
你的遭遇非我所願
I don't want that for you.
你撐住門
You keep it closed.
我再去找些東西來擋
I'll get more for the barricade.
你沒有站錯邊
Wasn't the wrong side.
如果萊克薩死的時候  地表人的軍隊還在那裡
If the grounder army was still there when Lexa died,
他們就會展開襲擊  你很清楚
they would have attacked, and you know it.
我想像你那麼看待事物
I wanted to see things like you.
我需要那樣  讓自己相信
I needed that, to believe
他們是壞人  而我們是好人
that they were bad and we were good.
我不知道自己還相信什麼
I don't know what I believe anymore.
我只知道我得背負著自己的所作所為生活下去
I just know I have to live with what I've done.
我不信
I don't believe it.
什麼  你找到自殺指令了嗎
What, did you find the kill switch?
別回答  阿莉能聽到我們說話
Don't answer that. ALIE can hear us.
我在讀取她的代碼  哈珀
I'm reading her code, Harper.
阿莉已經知道了
ALIE already knows.
知道什麼  你在說什麼
Knows what? What are you talking about?
克拉克在光之城
Clarke is in the City of Light.
艾比  艾比  有狀況
Abby, Abby, we've got a problem.
快來
Hey, hey, come on.
走開  她情況驟然惡化
Move. She's crashing.
克拉克得到的夜之血脈會不夠
Clarke's not getting enough nightblood.
她的身體已經開始排斥火種
Her body is already rejecting the flame.
你來接手
You need to take over.
照我現在的做法做
Do exactly what I'm doing.
來
Come on.
如果血液停止流入輸送管
If the blood stops flowing through this tube,
克拉克的大腦會溶解
Clarke's brain will liquefy.
等等  克拉克吞下了芯片嗎
Wait. Clarke took the chip?
她可能不得不那麼做吧  只是...
She would've had to, but--
怎麼了
What?
阿莉在運行一個新子程序找她
ALIE's running a flush subroutine to find her,
她把克拉克的代碼發送給了所有人
sending Clarke's code out to everyone.
-她就像個病毒  -的確
- Like she's a virus. - Exactly.
如果阿莉能控制她
ALIE wouldn't have to do that
就無需這麼大費周章
if she could control her.
看來克拉克在運行一個不同的程序
It's like Clarke is running a different program.
她把火种放進了自己的腦袋嗎
Did she put the flame in her head?
你不用小聲說
You don't need to whisper.
我知道克拉克植入了另一個人工智能
I'm aware Clarke has merged with the other A.I.
多虧了她  我的代碼現在
Thanks to her, my code is now updating
正在更新至第二代程序
to version 2 of my program.
阿莉更新完會怎麼樣
What happens when ALIE is updated?
她會刪除自殺指令
She'll delete the kill switch.
我們就沒辦法阻止她了
We won't be able to stop her.
所以趕快找到那該死的自殺指令
So find the damn kill switch.
萊克薩
Lexa?
最新美劇下載
www.ZiMuZu.tv
天吶
Oh, my god.
我們的戰鬥還沒結束
Our fight is not over.
不對勁  我不行了
Something's wrong. I can't.
我從沒想過還能再見你
I never thought I'd see you again.
我說過  我的意志會做出明智的選擇
I told you my spirit would choose wisely.
是什麼
What is it?
阿莉知道你在這裡
ALIE knows you're here.
她在從你的意志裡上傳火種
She's uploading the flame from your mind.
你的意志在改變週遭
Your mind is changing things.
日夜轉換  下雨
Day turns to night. It rains.
我們得趕快
We have to hurry.
克拉克
Clarke?
沒用了  扯開她的衣服
It's not working. Open her shirt.
她還是供血不足
She's still not getting enough blood.
我們得增加安塔麗的心率
We have to increase Ontari's heart rate.
克拉克  克拉克
Clarke. Clarke?
我一定不會想看的  對吧
I'm not gonna like this, am I?
艾比  動作快一點  好嗎
Abby, you need to move faster, ok?
克拉克  克拉克  回來
Clarke? Clarke, come back.
過來
Get over here.
我要你給她的心臟加壓
I need you to pump her heart.
什麼  你瘋了嗎
What? Are-- are you crazy?
我不要給她的心臟加壓
I'm not gonna pump her heart.
快
Now!
沒事的  就在下面
It's ok. Right under there.
-天啊  -沒事的
- Oh, god. - It's ok. Ok.
你做得很好
You're doing great.
去看看克拉克  這裡有我
Ok. Just go get Clarke. I got this.
拜託  寶貝
Come on, my baby.
挺住  挺住
Fight. Fight.
我知道你可以的
I know you can do it.
克拉克  醒醒  我們需要你
Clarke, come back. We need you.
穩定下來了  不要停
She's stabilizing. Don't stop what you're doing.
好了
Ok.
聽著
Listen to me.
現在上傳已經開始
Now the upload has begun,
阿莉的人現在可以看到我們
ALIE's people will be able to see us.
我們需要更加小心
We need to be more careful.
他們現在為什麼還沒來
Why aren't they here already?
火種會提供一些保護
The flame offers some protection,
但保護會越來越少
but less and less.
能站起來嗎
Can you stand?
可以
Yeah.
我爸爸的表  在走
My father's watch, it's working.
在倒數
It's counting down.
我們還有十分鐘時間去找到自殺指令
We have 10 minutes to find that kill switch.
謝謝你  貝卡
Thank you, Becca.
走
Come on.
小心
Look out.
上面
Over.
這個撐不了多久的
This isn't gonna hold for long.
他們是怎麼進來的
How the hell they even get in here?
都不重要了
Doesn't matter.
我們要在這裡阻止他們
This is where we make our stand.
聽起來人數不少
Sounds like there's a lot of them.
或許是時候去拿槍了
May be time to go to guns.
我們有比槍更管用的東西
We got something better than guns--
驚喜
Surprise.
我們走
Let's go.
等下  凱恩
Wait, Kane.
等下  我投降
Wait. I give up.
我願意吞下芯片
I'll take the chip.
很好  不會再有人會死了
Good. No one else has to die ever.
或許你可以勸你的導師也投降
Maybe you can convince your mentor of that.
-因陀羅還活著  -沒錯
- Indra's alive? - Yes...
在十字架上受著不必要的痛苦
On the cross suffering needlessly.
現在
Now!
已經沒電了
The charge is clear.
趕緊去拿他們的武器
Hurry up. Let's get their weapons.
等等  她不見了
Wait! We're losing her.
-是防火墻  -我不懂
- It's a firewall. - I don't understand.
你們永遠找不到自殺指令的
You'll never get to the kill switch.
-不要過來  -沒事
- No. - It's ok.
賈斯珀  你在這裡做什麼
Jasper, what are you doing here?
阻止你
Trying to stop you.
你已經見識過光之城了
You've seen the City of Light now.
這裡很完美
It's perfect.
這裡祥和  幸福  平安
There's peace, happiness, safety.
你為什麼要阻止大家領略這些
Why would you want to deny that to anyone?
為了讓人們來光之城  她折磨他們  賈斯珀
She's torturing people to get them here, Jasper,
奪取和控制他們的記憶
taking their memories, controlling them.
你現在根本不是你自己  是阿莉
This isn't even you. This is ALIE.
她必須這樣做
She's doing what has to be done.
她搶走了我們選擇的權利
She took away our choice.
人類有自由意志
Human beings have free will.
要怎麼活著  我們自己做主
We get to decide how we should live.
人類是唯一一個為了自己的利益
Human beings are the only species
自相殘殺的物種
that act against their own self-interest.
我們折磨彼此
We torture each other.
我們掀起戰爭  傷害彼此
We fight, hurt each other,
讓彼此心碎
break each other's hearts.
而在這裡沒有這些
None of that exists here.
阿莉保護我們不受自己的傷害
ALIE is protecting us from ourselves.
克拉克  還有時間
Clarke, there's still time.
我們會找到其他信號的  走吧
We'll find another sign. Let's go.
不能讓你們這樣做
We can't let you do that.
克拉克  你無處可逃了
Clarke, there's nowhere to run.
結束了  第二代人工智能不能再保護你了
It's over. The second A.I. can no longer protect you.
如果我把火種拿出來
If I remove the flame,
會阻止更新嗎
will it stop the update?
會  但沒有人自己選擇過拿出火種
Yes, but no one's ever done that by choice before.
不管怎樣  你會變成和他們一樣
Regardless, you'll be one of them.
而阿莉還是會得到火種
ALIE will get the flame either way.
不要再抵抗了
Stop fighting.
克拉克
Clarke.
拜託  克拉克  相信我
Come on, Clarke. Trust me.
是雷文
Raven.
賈斯珀 走開
Jasper, get out of the way.
不能讓他們過來
We can't let them follow.
快去  我拖住他們
Go. I'll hold them off.
不  萊克薩
No, Lexa.
我愛你
I love you.
我會永遠在你身邊
I'll always be with you.
她做到了  她進去了
She did it. She's in.
現在就看克拉克的了
Now it's up to Clarke.
氣閘關閉
Airlock sealed.
司令
Commander...
很高興你做到了
I'm glad you made it.
你是初代赫達貝卡
You're Becca pramheda.
貝卡沒事
Becca's fine.
沒時間了  代碼馬上就要更新了
There isn't much time. The code is nearly updated.
是你給我的這個嗎
Did you give me this?
不  是你
No. You did.
阿莉二代和你的大腦融合了
Alie 2.0 has merged with your mind,
但是你的意志在掌控地位
but your mind is in control,
只有在掌控地位的大腦
and only the mind that's in control
才能操作自殺指令
can operate the kill switch.
這就是了
This is it.
如果你扳動它
If you pull that...
你會殺死所有人
you will be killing everyone.
自己來看
See for yourself.
之前被炸彈炸燬的核電站
The nuclear power plants that were destroyed by the bombs
已經開始熔化
have begun to melt down.
四個月前我的無人機探測到了先熔化的幾個
My drones detected the first of them 4 months ago.
世界上還有超過十二個
There are more than a dozen at-risk plants
高危核電站  其中七個正在燃燒
around the world, 7 currently burning.
全球的輻射強度已經在上升了
Global radiation levels are already rising.
根據我的計算  不到六個月
By my calculations, in less than 6 months,
96%的地球表面將不適合人類生存
96% of the earth's surface will be uninhabitable...
即使在宇宙出生的人也一樣
even for those born in space.
所以  只有光之城
So, you see, the City of Light
才能拯救你們
is the only thing that can save you.
就這樣
This is it.
要保證克拉克的安全  給她時間
We need to keep Clarke safe, give her time.
他們沒有武器  但感覺不到痛苦
They're unarmed, but they won't feel pain,
只有打昏他們才會停止
and they won't stop until they're out cold.
收到  擊倒戰術
Copy that. Go for the knockout.
他們過了你這關我才會用槍
Only if they get past you.
先是黑雨
Black rain will come first.
然後地球將沒有飲用水
There will be no drinkable water.
癌前期病變會形成...
Precancerous lesions will form on--
她在拖延時間
She's stalling.
一旦更新完成
As soon as the update is complete,
她會刪掉自殺指令
she'll delete the kill switch.
上
Here we go.
我沒有在拖延時間
I am not stalling.
我說的都是實話
I'm telling the truth.
為什麼現在才說
Why tell us now?
如果是真的  為什麼不用
If it's true, why not use this
這個原因讓人們吞下芯片
to get people to take the chip
而是折磨他們
instead of torturing them?
上一次我警告我的創造者
The last time I warned my creator
人類生存受到威脅
of a threat to human survival,
她選擇把我鎖起來
she chose to lock me away
並且來這裡研究我的替代品
and came here to work on my replacement.
定義"反常例示"
Define "Perverse instantiation."
反常例示  為了實現
Perverse instantiation-- the implementation
有益目標而使用人類程序員無法預料的
Of a benign final goal through deleterious methods
有害方法
unforeseen by a human programmer.
比如殺死65億人
Like killing 6.5 billion people
來解決人口過剩
to solve overpopulation.
實現目標並不是全部  阿莉
The goal isn't everything, ALIE.
如何達成目標也很重要
How you reach the goal matters, too.
很抱歉我沒有教你這些
I'm sorry that I didn't teach you that.
克拉克  拜託  我們快擋不住了
Clarke, come on! We can't hold them off.
成敗在此一舉了  克拉克
It's now or never, Clarke.
一旦阿莉升級
Once ALIE's upgraded,
我就無法再幫助你了
I won't be able to help you anymore.
但我會幫你  在光之城
But I will...in the City of Light.
你不必再背負
You don't have to bear the burden
這些決定的負重  克拉克
of decisions like this one, Clarke.
你不必再繼續活在
You don't have to live with the pain
此前所做的事
of the things that you've done anymore,
你取走的和你失去的生命的痛苦裡
the lives that you have taken, and those you've lost.
你會獲得安寧
You will be at peace.
你會獲得永生
You will live forever.
我曾經試圖逃避痛苦
I've tried running away from my pain.
但沒有用
It doesn't work.
你的同伴可不同意  克拉克
Your people don't agree, Clarke.
你聽到賈斯珀說的話了
You heard Jasper.
即使是那些被強迫而來的人
Even those who were coerced
還是會選擇留在這裡
would still choose to stay here.
給他們真正的選擇
Give them a real choice,
我就不拉這個手柄
and I won't pull this lever.
把痛苦還給他們
Give them back their pain,
把記憶還給他們
their memories.
讓他們自己做決定
Let them decide for themselves.
她做不到
She can't.
她的核心指令是讓人類的生活更美好
Her core command is to make life better for mankind.
她仍舊認為自己在那麼做
She still thinks she's doing that.
二十秒後  自殺指令就會消失
20 seconds, and the kill switch will be gone.
你真的要讓人類
Would you really condemn the human race
在六個月內滅絕嗎
to die in 6 months?
我們能想出應對的辦法的
We'll figure something out.
我們總能做到
We always do.
是的  克拉克  希望永遠都在
Yes, Clarke. There's still hope.
根據我的計算  沒有
According to my calculations, there is not.
十秒
10 seconds.
讓我緩解他們的痛苦  克拉克
Let me ease their pain, Clarke.
我們可以一起拯救人類
We can save the human race together.
痛苦不能靠緩解  而是要克服
You don't ease pain. You overcome it...
而我們能做到
And we will.
克拉克
Clarke.
你做到了
You did it.
幫了點小忙吧
Little help here?
我們得移除火種
We need to remove the flame.
謝謝
Thank you.
只是地表的另一天  對吧
Just another day on the ground, right?
約翰
John...
對不起  約翰
Oh, I'm sorry, John.
沒事的  沒事的
That's ok. It's ok.
去吧
Go to him.
我沒事
I'm ok.
我們要怎麼知道她有沒有做到
How will we know she did it?
她做到了
She did it.
賈斯珀
Jasper.
這是真正的你嗎
Is it really you?
我好不容易感到快樂了
I was finally happy.
賈斯珀
Jasper...
我知道這世界很操蛋
I know this world can suck,
但起碼是真實的
but at least it's real.
我們能一起挺過去
We can get through this together.
你真的相信嗎
You really believe that?
我們會重新找到快樂的
We will be happy again,
我保證
I promise.
對不起我刺傷了你
I'm sorry I stabbed you.
對不起我開槍打了你
I'm sorry I shot you.
你不說我還沒感覺到
I didn't feel it.
慢點  慢點
Easy, easy.
等等
Hold on.
對不起  蒙蒂
I'm sorry, Monty.
沒事的
That's ok.
感覺要喝一杯
Could use a drink.
是啊  我們一起喝一杯
Yeah. We all could.
這輪我請了
This round's on me.
我扶你
Let me help you.
不用  我可以
Oh, no. I've got it.
阿莉消失了
ALIE's gone.
是啊  看出來了
Yeah. I figured.
克拉克  你表現得並不像
Clarke, you're not acting like someone
一個剛剛拯救了世界的人
who just saved the world.
因為我們沒有
Because we didn't...
還沒有
Not yet.
█
一大波正版授權“權力的遊戲”周邊向你靠近！
手機淘寶掃瞄左側二維碼
一起加入劇粉隊伍～
搜索微信公眾號
宅電舍動漫 有福利哦
█
特別鳴謝人人影視